

# **Ishan Sharma**

# **Data Analyst**

https://github.com/Ishanatri133

#### **Profile**

Hello, I am Ishan, a third-year student at VIPS-TC, deeply passionate about technology, the cosmos, and football. My diverse skill set includes web development and machine learning, where I excel.

In addition to my broad interests, I possess proficiency as a data analyst and Flutter developer. My contributions to various start-ups have encompassed roles such as Business Development and Public Relations, Consulting Intern, UI/UX Designer, Business Analyst Quality Assurance, and Data Analysis. This wealth of experience has not only refined my communication and public speaking skills but also equipped me to excel in the realms of data analysis and mobile app development.

## **Professional Experience**

•	
Contributor, GirlScript Summer of CodeGirl 2023  Made a few projects in flutter, web development and deep learning	05/2023 – 07/2023 Delhi, India
<ul> <li>Co-founder, PeacePal</li> <li>Mental Health AI chatbot startup focused on assisting people with mental health</li> <li>Got selected for the first round in Nasscom foundation</li> </ul>	03/2023 – 05/2023 Delhi, India
<ul> <li>Business Analyst Quality Assurance, CoachBudy</li> <li>Delivered high-quality, perfectly-functioning software and web applications to customers.</li> <li>Ensured the final product satisfied business objectives and user expectations.</li> <li>Made the documentation for both the testing and production site</li> </ul>	12/2022 – 02/2023 Gurgaon, India
<ul> <li>Graphic designer, Burst Bubble Studios</li> <li>Built assets for games using adobe illustrator and photoshop</li> <li>Monitored, tracked, and reported on feedback and online reviews</li> <li>Made the UI for the game</li> <li>link ☑</li> </ul>	10/2022 – 11/2022 Delhi, India
<ul> <li>Consulting Intern, Kalam Solutions</li> <li>Collected and maintained data on various topics</li> <li>Made reports for many startups</li> </ul>	09/2022 – 09/2022 Gurgaon, India
Business Development and Public relations, CoachBudy  • Data entry	07/2022 – 08/2022 Gurgaon, India

## **Education**

**Google Analytics** 

MySQL

B.Tech AI & ML, GGSIPU, New Delhi 11/2021 – present Delhi, India **Schooling,** Kendriya Vidyalaya 04/2009 - 07/2021 Delhi, India **Projects** YT clone Flutter 🛮 Notes App Flutter 🛮 Face Detection Python 🛮 Spotify Analysis using Python ☑ Weather App 🛮 Digital Resume 🛮 **Interests** • Football • Learning about Universe • Technology • Geopolitics Skills Web Development Python Flutter Figma

Power BI